[{"answer": "Well, what did you want", "docId": "sling_blade.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Naw, we don't have biscuits", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": " Did you decide, sir", "docId": "sling_blade.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Well, I guess it's all good", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "sling_blade.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Different ones. One's the Bible. One of 'ems a book on Christmas. One of 'ems how to be a carpenter", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Ain't got nowhere to set 'em down", "docId": "sling_blade.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "I did live there in the state hospital", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Don't you live somewhere", "docId": "sling_blade.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Why'd you live there", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I don't think I've ever seen you before", "docId": "sling_blade.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "It's been here seventeen years. Did you live here before or something", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "'Cause he didn't have enough money to take care of us the way he wanted to. That's what the letter said. He got laid off from work and had to just work odd jobs. I thought he took care of us fine.  my friend, did you really kill somebody", "docId": "sling_blade.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Who did you kill", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "my friend, you're awful. You shouldn't be that way", "docId": "sling_blade.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "He's just mentally retarded, I guess", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Ain't that the sweetest thing. What am I supposed to do about supper with you traipsin' around with that fag", "docId": "sling_blade.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Boy, ain't you somethin' else. Talkin' back and everything. It kinda makes me horny when you talk back", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "You're just crazy in a retarded kind of way then.  It wouldn't matter to me if you did do violence on somebody 'cause I ain't afraid of shit. You think I'm afraid for you to stay here. You're just a humped over retard it looks like to me. Not really, I'm just jokin' with you. Welcome to our humble home, buddy. my friend needs all the friends he can get. my friend's a real weak little kid. His daddy taught him how to be a pussy", "docId": "sling_blade.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": " Don't talk about daddy. Y'all go on to the garage and let me be", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "I reckon it tastes pretty good to me", "docId": "sling_blade.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I like the way you talk", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "sling_blade.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Please my friend, don't", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "We run outta somethin' to drink. Goin' to the county line. You want to race", "docId": "sling_blade.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Catch you later my friend", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "What are you doin' up again, my friend? You need to get a little sleep", "docId": "sling_blade.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Yeah, he has to go to work in a little while. I do too", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Did my friend go home", "docId": "sling_blade.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Did Karl go to bed", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Huh", "docId": "sling_blade.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Yeah, honey, someday everything's gonna be all right", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "I wouldn't mind a havin' supper", "docId": "sling_blade.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "I like my friend. He's a good boy. Me and him's made friends", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "If you want me to", "docId": "sling_blade.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "I bet he will. I got a little money if he don't. I'll get 'em for ye", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Yes sir. Right then it was", "docId": "sling_blade.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "A little ol' boy", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "I don't reckon I know. I ain't found no way yet and I'm three or four times as old as you. Might be that's just the way folks is", "docId": "sling_blade.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Make believin' always made me feel good too from time to time", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Well, okay. I got you some", "docId": "sling_blade.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Where'd he go? What's goin' on", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Reckon what kind of a feelin'", "docId": "sling_blade.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Will ye do somethin' for me if I ast you to", "qsentId": 44}]